Allocation (5pts, 7pts)

Practice Submissions
You have not attempted this problem.

Last updated: Feb 26 2021, 11:37
Problem
Analysis

Problem

There are N houses for sale. The i-th house costs Ai dollars to buy. You have a budget of B dollars to spend.

What is the maximum number of houses you can buy?
Input

The first line of the input gives the number of test cases, T. T test cases follow. Each test case begins with a single line containing the two integers N and B. The second line contains N integers. The i-th integer is Ai, the cost of the i-th house.
Output

For each test case, output one line containing Case #x: y, where x is the test case number (starting from 1) and y is the maximum number of houses you can buy.
Limits

Time limit: 15 seconds per test set.
Memory limit: 1GB.
1 ≤ T ≤ 100.
1 ≤ B ≤ 105.
1 ≤ Ai ≤ 1000, for all i.
Test set 1

1 ≤ N ≤ 100.
Test set 2

1 ≤ N ≤ 105.
--------------------
Sample:

Input

3
4 100
20 90 40 90
4 50
30 30 10 10
3 300
999 999 999
  
Output	

Case #1: 2
Case #2: 3
Case #3: 0
------------------
  

In Sample Case #1, you have a budget of 100 dollars. You can buy the 1st and 3rd houses for 20 + 40 = 60 dollars.
In Sample Case #2, you have a budget of 50 dollars. You can buy the 1st, 3rd and 4th houses for 30 + 10 + 10 = 50 dollars.
In Sample Case #3, you have a budget of 300 dollars. You cannot buy any houses (so the answer is 0).

Note: Unlike previous editions, in Kick Start 2020, all test sets are visible verdict test sets, meaning you receive instant feedback upon submission.
